Finding Aid for Philip A. Hart Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- Subject files, 1959-1976; 96 linear feet
  - 1974
    - Parks and Recreation
      - Pictured Rocks (Box 218)
      - Sleeping Bear Dunes, 2 folders (Box 218)
      - Wilderness Areas (Box 218)
    - Political Affairs
      - General (Box 218)
      - Campaigns (Box 218)
      - Michigan Campaigns (Box 218)
      - PAH (for President, etc.) (Box 218)
    - Pollution
      - Air Pollution (Box 218)
      - Solid Waste (Box 218)
    - Servicemen and Veterans
      - Amnesty, 2 folders (Box 218)
    - State Government
      - Daylight Saving Time (Box 218)
      - Lotteries (Box 218)
      - Natural Resources, Dept. of (Box 218)
    - Taxes
      - Charitable Deduction Petition (Box 219)
      - Deductions (Box 219)
      - Evasions (Box 219)
      - Exemptions (Box 219)
      - Federal (Box 219)
    - Trade
      - General (Box 219)
      - Iron Mountain (Box 219)
      - Jones Act, Great Lakes Cruising (Box 219)
      - Mass Transit (Box 219)
      - Trade Expansion -- Fair Trade (Box 219)
  - 1975
    - Agriculture
      - Agriculture, Dept. of (Box 219)
      - Farm Programs (Box 219)
      - PBB (Box 219)
      - Soil Survey and Conservation (Box 219)
      - Tobacco (Box 219)
      - Wheat (Box 219)
    - Appropriations
      - Budget, 3 folders (Box 219)
      - Budget-Impoundment (Box 219)
      - Government (Box 219)
      - Interior (Box 219)
      - Military Spending (Box 219)
    - Civil Rights
      - Constitutional Rights (Box 219)
      - Discrimination (Box 219)
      - Equal Opportunities (Box 219)
      - Freedom of Information (Box 219)
      - Freedom of Press (Box 219)
      - Freedom of Religion (Box 219)
      - Invasion of Privacy (Box 219)
      - Voting Rights (Box 219)
      - Women's Rights (Box 219)
      - Consumer Protection, 2 folders (Box 219)
    - Communications
      - Television, 2 folders (Box 220)
    - Congress
      - General (Box 220)
      - A and M, Copper Range by AMAX (Box 220)
      - Antitrust and Monopoly (Box 220)
      - Black Caucus (Box 220)
      - CIA, Select Committee on (Box 220)
      - Commerce, Committee on (Box 220)
      - Criticism (Box 220)
      - Ethics of Members (Box 220)
      - Financial Disclosure (Box 220)
      - Intelligence, Select Committee, 2 folders (Box 220)
      - Internal Security, Subcommittee on (Box 220)
      - Joint Letters, 2 folders (Box 220)
      - Judiciary, Committee on the (Box 220)
      - Organization and Reorganization (Box 220)
      - Rural Development Subcommittee (Box 220)
      - Senate Small Business Committee (Box 220)
      - Technology Assessment, Office of (Box 220)
    - Crime
      - Abolition on Death Penalty (Box 220)
      - Criminal Procedure (Box 220)
      - Gun Control, 3 folders (Box 220)
      - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 220)
      - Product Safety (Box 220)
    - Defense Affairs
      - Chemical and Biological (Box 220)
      - Chrysler Corporation (Box 220)
      - Equipment (Box 220)
      - National Security (Box 220)
      - Project Sanguine (Box 220)
      - Sanguine (Box 220)
      - Weapons (Box 220)
    - Economy
      - General, 3 folders (Box 220)
      - Inflation (Box 220)
      - Michigan Industry (Box 221)
      - National Economy, 4 folders (Box 221)
      - National Priorities (Box 221)
      - Wage and Price Controls (Box 221)
    - Education
      - Health, Education and Welfare (Box 221)
      - Integration (busing) (Box 221)
    - Elections
      - Campaign Financing (Box 221)
      - Electoral College (Box 221)
      - National Primaries (Box 221)
      - Popular Vote (Box 221)
      - Reform (Box 221)
      - Voting Practices (Box 221)
    - Energy
      - Conservation (Box 221)
      - Electric Power, 2 folders (Box 221)
      - Energy Conservation (Box 221)
      - Gas (natural gas) (Box 221)
      - Nuclear Power (Box 221)
      - Nuclear Power-Safety (Box 221)
      - Oil, 4 folders (Box 221)
      - Solar Energy (Box 221)
    - Executive Branch
      - Cabinet, the (Box 221)
      - CIA (Central Intelligence Agency) (Box 221)
      - President, the (Box 221)
      - Vice-President, the (Box 221)
    - Foreign Relations
      - Angola (Box 222)
      - Chile (Box 222)
      - China (Box 222)
      - Civilian Prisoner Exchange (Box 222)
      - Foreign Aid, 4 folders (Box 222)
      - Foreign Policy (Box 222)
      - Genocide (Box 222)
      - Israel (Box 222)
      - Korea (Box 222)
      - Middle East (Box 222)
      - Salt (Box 222)
      - Treaties (Box 222)
      - United Nations (Box 222)
      - USSR, 2 folders (Box 222)
      - Vietnam, 4 folders (Box 222)
      - Vietnam Families (Box 222)
    - Health and Welfare
      - Abortions, 3 folders (Box 222)
      - Alcoholism (Box 222)
      - FDA (Food and Drug Administration) (Box 222)
      - Narcotics (Box 222)
      - Population Control (Box 222)
      - Smoking (Box 222)
    - Highways
      - I-475 (Box 222)
      - I-94 (Box 222)
      - State (Box 222)
      - US-2 (Box 222)
    - Housing and Urban Development
      - Forest Park Funding (Box 222)
    - Indian Affairs
      - General (Box 223)
      - Education (Box 223)
      - Equal Opportunity (Box 223)
      - Health (Box 223)
      - Housing (Box 223)
      - Information (Box 223)
    - Insurance and Retirement
      - Medical Malpractice Insurance (Box 223)
      - Medicare (Box 223)
      - Pension Reform (Box 223)
      - Social Security (Box 223)
    - Judiciary
      - American Bar Association (Box 223)
      - Criminal Code (Box 223)
      - FBI-Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 223)
      - LEAA-Law Enforcement Assistance Administration, 2 folders (Box 223)
      - Michigan Supreme Court (Box 223)
      - Reform (Box 223)
      - Special Prosecutor (Box 223)
      - U.S. Circuit Court (Box 223)
      - U.S. District Court (Box 223)
    - Labor
      - Illegal Aliens (Box 223)
      - Migrant Labor (Box 223)
      - Strikes, 2 folders (Box 223)
      - Unions, 3 folders (Box 223)
    - Natural Resources
      - General (Box 223)
      - Conservation (Box 223)
      - Fish and Wildlife (Box 223)
      - Land (Box 223)
      - Minerals (Box 223)
    - Nominations
      - Ambassadors (Box 223)
      - CIA, Nomination of George Bush (Box 223)
      - Interior-Hathaway (Box 223)
      - Levi, Atty. Gen. (Box 223)
      - Meskill, Thomas J. (Box 223)
      - Staebler, Neil (Box 223)
      - U.S. Supreme Court (Box 223)
    - Parks and Recreation
      - Pictured Rocks (Box 224)
      - Sex Discrimination (Box 224)
      - Sleeping Bear Dunes (Box 224)
    - Political Affairs
      - Committees (Box 224)
      - Democratic Party, 2 folders (Box 224)
      - Kennedy for President (Box 224)
      - PAH Campaign (Box 224)
      - PAH for President (Box 224)
    - Pollution
      - Air Pollution (Box 224)
      - Environmental Education (Box 224)
      - EPA (Environmental Protection Agency) (Box 224)
      - Pollution Control Equipment (Box 224)
      - Water (Box 224)
    - Servicemen and Veterans
      - Amnesty, 2 folders (Box 224)
    - Taxes
      - Deductions (Box 224)
      - Exemptions (Box 224)
      - Federal (Box 224)
      - Federal Income (Box 224)
      - IRS (Internal Revenue Service) (Box 224)
      - Reform (Box 224)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box 224)
    - Trade
      - East/West (Box 224)
      - Imports (Box 224)
    - Transportation
      - Air (Box 224)
      - Mass Transit (Box 224)
      - Motor (Box 224)
      - Motor Carrier (Box 224)
  - 1976
    - Agriculture
      - Cherries (Box 225)
      - Farm Home Administration (Box 225)
      - Farm Programs (Box 225)
      - PBB (Box 225)
      - Tobacco (Box 225)
      - Wheat (Box 225)
    - Appropriations
      - Budget, 2 folders (Box 225)
      - DOD, Department of Defense (Box 225)
      - Government Spending (Box 225)
      - Military Spending, 2 folders (Box 225)
    - Civil Rights
      - General (Box 225)
      - Constitutional Rights (Box 225)
      - Discrimination (Box 225)
      - Equal Opportunities (Box 225)
      - Freedom of Press (Box 225)
      - Freedom of Religion (Box 225)
      - Invasion of Privacy (Box 225)
      - Voting Rights (Box 225)
      - Women's Rights (Box 225)
    - Commerce
      - Consumer Protection (Box 225)
      - Product Safety (Box 225)
    - Communications
      - FCC, Federal Communications Commission (Box 225)
      - Radio (Box 225)
      - Television (Box 225)
    - Congress
      - Antitrust and Monopoly (Box 225)
      - Committees (Box 225)
      - Criticism (Box 225)
      - Compulsory Retirement (Box 225)
      - Duties and Attendance (Box 225)
      - Ethics of Members (Box 225)
      - Finance Committees (Box 225)
      - Financial Disclosure (Box 225)
      - Intelligence, Select Committee on (Box 225)
      - Internal Security, Subcommittee on (Box 225)
      - Joint Economic Committee (Box 225)
      - Joint Letters (Box 225)
      - Multi-National Corporations, Subcommittee on (Box 225)
      - Nutrition and Human Needs, Select Committee (Box 225)
      - Obscenity and Pornography, Committee (Box 225)
      - Operations Costs (Box 225)
      - Organization and Reorganization (Box 225)
    - Crime
      - Abolition of Death Penalty (Box 226)
      - Criminal Procedure (Box 226)
      - Gun Control, 2 folders (Box 226)
      - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 226)
      - Prevention (Box 226)
    - Defense Affairs
      - Equipment (Box 226)
      - Kincheloe Air Force Base, 4 folders (Box 226)
      - Project Seafarer (Box 226)
      - Weapons (Box 226)
    - Economy
      - National Economy (Box 226)
    - Education
      - Integration (Box 226)
    - Elections
      - Campaign Financing (Box 226)
      - Electoral College (Box 226)
      - National Primaries (Box 226)
      - Reform (Box 226)
      - Voting Practices (Box 226)
    - Energy
      - Electric Power (Box 226)
      - Gas (Box 226)
      - Nuclear Power, 2 folders (Box 226)
      - Oil (Box 226)
      - Solar Energy (Box 226)
    - Executive Branch
      - General (Box 226)
      - Cabinet (Box 226)
      - CIA, Central Intelligence Agency (Box 226)
      - President (Box 226)
    - Finance
      - NYC (Box 226)
    - Foreign Relations
      - General (Box 227)
      - Africa (Box 227)
      - Angola (Box 227)
      - China (Box 227)
      - Foreign Aid (Box 227)
      - Foreign Policy (Box 227)
      - Genocide (Box 227)
      - Israel (Box 227)
      - Korea (Box 227)
      - Panama Canal (Box 227)
      - State Department (Box 227)
      - Treaties (Box 227)
      - Turkey (Box 227)
      - United Nations (Box 227)
      - USSR (Box 227)
      - Vietnam (Box 227)
    - Health and Welfare
      - Abortions (Box 227)
      - Alcoholism (Box 227)
      - Cancer (Box 227)
      - Diseases (Box 227)
      - Laetrile (Box 227)
      - Narcotics, 3 folders (Box 227)
      - Population Control (Box 227)
      - Smoking (Box 227)
    - Highways
      - Environmental Assessment Handbook (Box 227)
      - Interstate (Box 227)
      - Safety (Box 227)
      - State (Box 227)
    - Indian Affairs
      - Bay Mills, Brimley (Box 228)
      - Detroit Indian Center (Box 228)
      - Dockets 18-E and 58 (Box 228)
      - Education (Box 228)
      - Federal Recognition (Box 228)
      - Grand River Ottawa District, S. 1659 (Box 228)
      - Hannahville, Wilson (Box 228)
      - Health (Box 228)
      - Indian Action Team (Box 228)
      - Indian Policy Review Commission (Box 228)
      - Indian Water Rights (Box 228)
      - Information (Box 228)
      - Interior-Bureau of Indian Affairs, Dept. of (Box 228)
      - Isabella, Mount Pleasant (Box 228)
      - Keweenaw Bay, Baraga (Box 228)
      - Michigan, Bureau of Indian Affairs (Box 228)
      - Michigan Indian Legal Service Corporation (Box 228)
      - Michigan Indians (Box 228)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box 228)
      - Sault Ste. Marie (Box 228)
      - Sterilization (Box 228)
      - Treaty Rights (Box 228)
      - Wounded Knee (Box 228)
    - Insurance and Retirement
      - Social Security, 2 folders (Box 228)
    - Judiciary
      - Criminal Code (Box 228)
      - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 228)
      - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration-LEAA, 2 folders (Box 228)
      - Justice, Department of (Box 228)
      - Reform (Box 228)
      - Unification Church (Box 228)
      - U.S. Circuit Court (Box 228)
      - U.S. District Court (Box 228)
      - U.S. Supreme Court (Box 228)
    - Labor
      - General (Box 229)
      - Labor, Department of (Box 229)
      - Migrant Labor (Box 229)
      - Situs Picketing (Box 229)
      - Strikes (Box 229)
      - Unemployment (Box 229)
      - Unions, 2 folders (Box 229)
    - Natural Resources
      - Conservation (Box 229)
      - Fish and Wildlife (Box 229)
      - Management (Box 229)
      - Minerals (Box 229)
    - Nominations
      - Federal Judges (Box 229)
      - U.S. Attorney (Box 229)
      - U.S. Supreme Court (Box 229)
    - Parks and Recreation
      - General (Box 229)
      - Grand Traverse Islands (Box 229)
      - Pictured Rocks (Box 229)
      - Sleeping Bear Dunes (Box 229)
    - Political Affairs
      - General (Box 229)
      - Carter, Jimmy for President (Box 229)
      - Committees (Box 229)
      - Contributions (Box 229)
      - Democratic Convention (Box 229)
      - Democratic Party (Box 229)
      - Kennedy for President (Box 229)
      - Michigan Campaigns (Box 229)
      - PAH -- Retirement (Box 229)
      - Donald Riegle Jr. (Box 229)
    - Pollution
      - General (Box 229)
      - Air Pollution (Box 229)
      - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 229)
      - Pollution Control Equipment (Box 229)
      - Recycling Solid Waste (Box 229)
      - Reserve Mining Co., 1973-1976 (Box 229)
      - Water (Box 229)
    - Servicemen and Veterans
      - Amnesty (Box 230)
      - Slovick (Box 230)
    - Taxes
      - General (Box 230)
      - Deductions (Box 230)
      - Evasions (Box 230)
      - Federal Income, 2 folders (Box 230)
      - IRS, 2 folders (Box 230)
      - Property (Box 230)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box 230)
    - Trade
      - Tariffs (Box 230)
    - Transportation
      - General (Box 230)
      - Air (Box 230)
      - Freight (Box 230)
      - Mass Transit (Box 230)
      - Motor, 2 folders (Box 230)
      - Rail (Box 230)
      - Safety (Box 230)
      - Ships (Box 230)
      - Water (St. Lawrence Seaway Development Corp.) (Box 230)
- Constituent correspondence, 1958-1976; 15 linear feet
  The Constituent Correspondence series (1958-1976; 15 linear ft.)shows the depth and intensity of Hart's constituents to the issues of the day. Depending upon the issue, the Hart office often received many thousands of letters urging Hart to vote yea or nay on some controversial piece of legislation. So voluminous was the senator's mail that beginning in 1966, he discarded the letters, keeping instead a record of the letters he received on any given issue. The files up through 1965 have been heavily sampled to provide a sense of what issues exercised his constituents. A more useful portion of this series is the form response that Hart used to reply to his constituents and the files of mail counts.
  Files for 1958-1959 are arranged by topic or legislative subject. Files for 1960-1965 are arranged by form letter response number; more or less chronologically)
  - 1958-1959
    (mainly 1959) (arranged by topic or legislative subject)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 231)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 232)
  - 1960 (Box 332)
  - 1960 (Box 233)
  - 1960 (Box 234)
  - 1961 (Box 234)
  - 1961 (Box 235)
  - 1961 (Box 236)
  - 1962 (Box 237)
  - 1962 (Box 238)
  - 1963 (Box 238)
  - 1964
    (includes .5 linear feet re Civil Rights Act)
    - 1964 (Box 238)
    - 1964 (Box 239)
    - 1964 (Box 240)
    - 1964 (Box 241)
  - 1965 (Box 241)
  - 1965 (Box 242)
  - 1965 (Box 243)
  - Mail Counts, 1967-1976 (Box 244)
  - Form letter responses, 1959-1971
    - 1959-1963 (Box 244)
    - 1964-1971 (Box 245)
  - Activity logs, 1975-1976 (Box 245)
  - Correspondence and other materials relating to the effort of Dr. Richard D. Mudd to obtain exonerations for Dr. Samuel A. Mudd as a conspirator in the assassination of President Abraham Lincoln, 1965-1976 (Box 245)
- Office files, 1959-1976; 13 linear feet
  Office Files (1959-1976; 13 linear ft.) is an artificial series made up of the combination of what were originally three separate series documenting some facet of the administration of the Hart office and some of the more mundane kinds of responsibilities that a senator performed for his constituents. Office Files now consists of three subseries: "General Files", "Administration" and "Publicity." "General Files" covers the period of 1959 through 1969 after which time the files seem to have merged with the "Administration" subseries which covers the period of 1959 to 1976. The kinds of documents originally contained in these two subseries included: recommendations requested for Washington jobs; PAH's acknowledgments of persons' graduations, anniversaries, birthdays, etc.; requests for flags to fly over the Capitol; requests for travel courtesy; requests for PAH to meet with visitors in Washington; requests from constituents for the Agricultural Yearbook, the Congressional Record, speeches made by PAH in Congress, and reports of government agencies; letters from applicants for intern positions or for positions as Capitol pages; and requests for Hart to use his influence to get other politicos to make speeches and/or public appearances. These series also included Hart's request to use rooms in the Capitol. These files have been heavily sampled, and in some cases, discarded completely. The researcher should note that in 1970, the year the "General Files" and "Administration" subseries merged, the character of the files changed significantly with many of the file headings disappearing altogether. Obviously in 1970, Hart and his staff either discarded or had microfilmed and then discarded letters and requests of a routine nature. Some of the more interesting files in the "Administration" subseries relate to staff operations and office administration. Here there are individual files for staff members containing correspondence and memoranda. The third subseries in the Office Files series is "Public Relations." Formerly a subseries under "Administration" series (called Administration - Publicity), around 1970, the files were split off from "Administration" and a separate series - "Public Relations" - was created. Types of files in the now "Public Relations" subseries include responses to Hart mailings (newsletters) or responses to his radio and TV appearances.
  - General, 1959-1966
    - 1959-1966 (Box 246)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 247)
    - 1969 (Box 248)
  - Administration, 1959-1976
    - 1959-1963 (Box 248)
    - 1959-1963 (Box 249)
    - 1964 (Box 250)
    - 1965 (Box 250)
    - 1966 (Box 250)
    - 1966 (Box 251)
    - 1967 (Box 251)
    - 1967 (Box 252)
    - 1968 (Box 252)
    - 1969 (Box 252)
    - 1969 (Box 253)
    - 1970 (Box 253)
    - 1971 (Box 253)
    - 1972 (Box 253)
    - 1973 (Box 254)
    - 1974 (Box 254)
    - 1975 (Box 254)
    - 1976 (Box 254)
  - Publicity / Public Relations, 1959-1976
    (File title changed to Public relation in 1970, 1964 and 1968 files not received)
    - 1959-1963 (Box 255)
    - 1965 (Box 256)
    - 1966 (Box 256)
    - 1969 (Box 256)
    - 1970 (Box 256)
    - 1970 (Box 257)
    - 1971 (Box 257)
    - 1972 (Box 257)
    - 1973 (Box 258)
    - 1974 (Box 258)
    - 1975 (Box 258)
    - 1976 (Box 258)
- Political files [unprocessed], 1958-1976; 5 linear feet, 3 oversize volumes
  The Political Files (1958-1976; 5 linear ft. and 3 oversize scrapbooks) consist of files of campaign materials and position papers covering Hart's three campaigns for the Senate: 1958, 1964, and 1970. The bulk of the files relate to the 1970 campaign when Hart ran against Lenore Romney. The files are divided by the three campaigns and are largely unprocessed. The researcher should also consult also consult heading "Political Affairs" in the series Subject Files
  - 1958-1964 (Box 259)
    (see also two scrapbooks, 1958, detailing campaign for the U.S. Senate; filed as AC Hart, Philip A)
  - Oversize Scrapbook (Volume 1)
  - Oversize Scrapbook (Volume 2)
  - Oversize Scrapbook (Volume 3)
  - Campaign, 1970 (Box 260)
  - Campaign, 1970 (Box 261)
  - Campaign, 1970 (Box 262)
  - Campaign, 1970 (Box 263)
  - Post-1970 files (Box 263)
- Miscellaneous, 1949-1976; 4 linear feet
  A small series of various files, the Miscellaneous series (1949-1976; 4 linear ft.) includes a small quantity of materials from the period before Hart came to the Senate, when he was in state government as State Securities Commissioner and Lieutenant Governor. One linear foot of material relates to Hart's work as a member of the National Commission on the Cause and Prevention of Violence in 1969. In addition there are microfiche copies of portions of the Hart papers, mainly copies of speeches, press releases, and Congressional Record statements. Filmed in a random order and without an easy-to-use index, the researcher is instead directed to the hard copy of the PRESS series for the needed information.
  - National Commission on the Cause and Prevention of Violence (Box 264)
  - Microfiche of selective portions of the Hart papers (Box 265)
  - Microfiche of selective portions of the Hart papers (Box 266)
  - Pre-1959 files
    - State Securities Commissioner papers, 1949-1950 candidate for Secretary of State (Box 267)
    - Scrapbook concerning campaign for Michigan Lieutenant Governor, 1954 (Volume AC)
    - United States Attorney, 1953 (Box 267)
    - Speeches, 1950 (Box 267)
    - Speeches, 1951 (Box 267)
    - Speeches, 1955 (Box 267)
    - Speeches, 1957 (Box 267)
    - Press releases-Lieutenant Governor, 1957-1958; 2 folders (Box 267)
    - Civil Rights, 3 folders (Box 267)
  - Awards, citations, diplomas (Box 267)
- Sound recordings
  [Digitized audio files are currently available only in the Bentley Historical Library reading room on designated Bentley Library computers.]
  The Sound recordings series consists largely of reel-to-reel tapes with some cassettes of Senator Hart appearances on radio programs and at various public forums.
  - Reel-to-reel (7 in.)
    (7 1/2 ips until otherwise indicated)
    - 1959 (Box 268)
      - Senator Philip A. Hart gives his impressions of being a senator, 1959 March; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 268)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-1-1]; (Hart discusses his life story, his political career, and beliefs.)
      - "Capitol Cloakroom" program, PAH discusses President Eisenhower's trip overseas, December 3, 1959 (Box 268)
        (tape no. 2)
    - :, 1960
      - WMCA-NYC PAH on Gov. Williams as potential candidate for President, May 1960 (Box 268)
        (tape no. 3)
      - "Speak Up" program with Marsha Rose, Hart discusses Democratic hopefuls including John F. Kennedy, 1960 June 12; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 268)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-4-1]; (Recording of a Television Broadcast, debating 1960 Presidential Election Democratic Hopefuls. Guests include: Philip A Hart (representing John F. Kennedy), Charles Brown (Missouri Congressman representing Stuart Symington), Miss India Edwards (Vice-Chairman of DNC, Co-Chair of Campaign representing LBJ), Henry Sawyer, (Co-Chairman of Pennsylvanians for Stevenson, representing Adlai Stevenson).)
    - 1961 (Box 268)
      - "Youth Wants to Know" Julian Barber interviews Philip A. Hart., 1961 February 23; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 268)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-5-1]; (Hart answers questions from youth on disarmament, economy, unemployment, education, hosted by Julian Barber.)
      - Glen Lake Park Meeting, part 1, August 30, 1961; 3 3/4 ips; poor recording (Box 268)
        (tape no. 6)